Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Family: Frances Ryan Thomas (found in Frances's personal papers), undated; 11 (Box 1574)
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas (?) standing outside], 10
    - [Frances Ryan standing beneath a palm tree], 11
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas (?) in a nurse uniform], 12
  - Subject files: Family: Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas, undated; 12 (Box 1574)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas], 2
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas, 3
    - [Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and others at a Christmas party], 4
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas], 5
    - Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas standing outside an automobile], 6
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas in costume], 7
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas in riding dress], 8
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas in riding dress], 9
    - [Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas in costume], 10
    - Note: [Mr. and Mrs. LT (?)], 11
  - Subject files: Family: Lowell Thomas (childhood), circa 1982 - 1900; 13 (Box 1574)
    - [Lowell Thomas and another young boy], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other children], 2
    - [Portraits of Lowell Thomas], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and his mother], 4
  Box 1575
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Family: Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr., undated; 1 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other men standing in the snow], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas pointing out something to a man in the snow], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. with skis], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. standing in front of a stuffed bear], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. standing in front of a stuffed bear], 5
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in fur coats], 6
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in fur coats], 7
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in fur coats in front of stuffed bear], 8
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in fur coats in front of stuffed polar bear], 9
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in fur coats], 10
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in fur coats], 11
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in fur coats in front of stuffed polar bear], 12
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in fur coats in front of stuffed polar bear], 13
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. in fur coats in front of stuffed polar bear], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas and man sitting on a plane, Lowell Thomas, Jr. in uniform in cockpit], 15
    - Note: Ludwick, LT, LT jr., 16
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. talking to a woman], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. standing outside], 18
  - Subject files: Family: Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and grandchildren, circa 1960s; 2 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas with their grandchildren], 1
    - Note [Mr. and Mrs. Thomas w/ Ann + David], 2
  - Subject files: Family: Lowell Thomas, Jr. and Mrs. Tay Thomas, Jr., circa 1940s - 1950s; 3 (Box 1575)
    - [A group of young boys], 1
    - [Young woman holding a football and petting a dog], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and a woman], 3
    - [Young woman smiling], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. standing with a woman outside], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. and a woman], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and three others standing around a flag], 7
  - Subject files: Family reunion, undated; 4 (Box 1575)
    - [Group of people at a family reunion], 1
    - [Group of people at a family reunion], 2
    - [Setting up the Christmas tree], 3
    - [Setting up the Christmas tree], 4
    - [People sitting in the living room, Lowell Thomas and Harry G. Thomas], 5
    - [People sitting in the living room, Lowell Thomas and Harry G. Thomas], 6
  - Subject files: Famous, undated; 5 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. (?) and three men standing by a lake], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with four men], 2
  - Subject files: First World Flight, 1924; 6 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with members of the First World Flight], 1
    - [Camels in front of First World Flight planes], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to First World Flyers], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and another pilot sitting in a plane], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas holding a ribbon for a man to cut-First World Flyers], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas with a man cutting a ribbon-First World Flyers], 6
    - [Camels standing in front of First World Flyer planes], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas with two First World Flyers], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas delivering a speech with the First World Flyers], 9
    - [First World Flyers looking at a globe], 10
    - [First World Flyers standing next to a plane], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas, Jr., inspecting part of downed plane], 12
    - [Man with downed plane], 13
    - [Man with downed plane], 14
    - [Man with downed plane], 15
    - [Man with downed plane], 16
    - [Man with downed plane], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas with the First World Flyers posing in front of plane, raccoon on right], 18
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other standing on a beach], 19
    - [Photos if Lowell Thomas and another man in a plane], 20
    - [Photos if Lowell Thomas and another man in a plane], 21
    - [Lowell Thomas and three First World Flyers leaning on a plane], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas and six First World Flyers], 23
  - Subject files: Fox Movietone, circa 1930s; 7 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas and three others looking at papers], 1
  - Subject files: Friends, undated; 8 (Box 1575)
    - [A man with fish on a string], 1
    - Note [Bryon Parks. Got LT involved in real estate], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two First World Flyers], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two First World Flyers], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two First World Flyers], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two First World Flyers], 6
    - [Photo of a First World Flyer], 7
    - [Photo of a First World Flyer], 8
    - [Photo of a First World Flyer], 9
    - [Photo of a First World Flyer], 10
  - Subject files: Golf, circa 1950 - 1970s; 9 (Box 1575)
    - [Golf score card], 1
    - [Golf score card], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and his golf friends], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with his golf friend], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and three golf friends], 5
  - Subject files: Greenville, Ohio, circa 1952 - 1968; 10 (Box 1575)
    - [Greenville Courtesy Card -Needs to be roated!], 1
    - Note [Woodington + Greenville], 2
    - [Man standing outside of a building in Greenville], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas giving out his book], 4
    - [Man playing pool], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) playing pool], 6
  - Subject files: Jack Girsham [for possible use in Burma Jack], undated; 11 (Box 1575)
    - Note [Description of the negatives], 1
    - [Jack Girsham with a tiger he shot], 2
    - [Jack Girsham with a tiger he shot], 3
    - [An elephant Jack Girsham shot], 4
    - [An elephant Jack Girsham shot], 5
    - [An elephant Jack Girsham shot], 6
    - [An elephant Jack Girsham shot], 7
    - [An elephant Jack Girsham shot], 8
    - [Jack Girsham with the tiger he killed], 9
    - [Woman (?) hunter and a dog], 10
    - [Boy standing in a village], 11
    - [Two boys holding birds], 12
    - [Two men sitting on a dead elephant], 13
    - [Jack Girsham sitting on a dead elephant], 14
    - [Men with a dead tiger, man on an elephant], 15
    - [Three men standing with a dead tiger], 16
    - [Girl in a village], 17
  - Subject files: Hammersley Hill, undated; 12 (Box 1575)
    - [House on the opposite side of a lake at Hammersley Hill], 1
    - [Large house at Hammersley Hill], 2
    - [Barn (?) at Hammersley Hill], 3
    - [Dirt road and shrubs at Hammersley Hill], 4
    - [Barn at Hammersley Hill], 5
    - [Hammersley Hill barn], 6
    - [Landscape at Hammersley Hill], 7
  - Subject files: Hawaiian Debating team and Lowell Thomas, circa 1940s; 13 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas with the Hawaiian Debating team], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and the Hawaiian Debating team], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and the Hawaiian Debating team], 3
    - Note [frontside], 4
    - Note [backside], 5
  - Subject files: "Heart Attack", 1963; 14 (Box 1575)
    - [Man in lederhosen], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with some men], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with some men], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with some men], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with some men], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with some men], 6
    - Note: photocopy of negatives, 7
    - Note: Minox processiog labratories film, 8
  - Subject files: Father Theodore Hesburgh, President of Notre Dame, circa 1960s; 15 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas, Fracnes Ryan Thomas, and Father Theodore Hesburgh watching a game], 1
  - Subject files: High Adventure with Lowell Thomas (New Guinea and Timbuktu), circa late 1950s; 16 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas riding a camel], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group of tribespeople], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with two tribespeople], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and two tribeswomen], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas with two tribesmen], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group of tribespeople.], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with a group of tribespeople], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group of tribespeople.], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with a group of tribespeople], 9
  - Subject files: Hollansburg, Ohio, undated; 17 (Box 1575)
    - [Man dressed up like a maid], 1
    - [A young boy holding eggs], 2
    - [Man sitting in a shop in Hollansburg, Ohio], 3
    - [Woman in the garden], 4
    - [Three women on the front porch], 5
    - [Woman in the yard with her dog], 6
    - [People standing around an automobile], 7
    - [Three people sitting in the grass with a dog], 8
    - [People standing around an automobile], 9
    - [David R. Thomas gravestone], 10
    - [Man and woman standing outside], 11
    - [House in Hollansburg, Ohio], 12
    - [Three people standing on a boat], 13
    - [A man and two women sitting on a porch], 14
    - [House on a dirt road in Hollansburg, Ohio], 15
    - [Church in Hollansburg, Ohio], 16
    - [Woman feeding the chickens], 17
    - [Two women standing in a yard], 18
    - [Two women standing in front of corn], 19
    - [Women standing in a yard], 20
    - [Two women in rocking chairs], 21
    - Note [Sat 5. Thomas. Hollandsban. Chas. G. Rosewell.], 22
  - Subject files: Honors, circa 1930 - 1976; 18 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas's Radio Commentator Award], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and another man at a commencement ceremony], 2
  - Subject files: Herbert Hoover(includes visit to Baghdad), circa 1940s - early 1950s; 19 (Box 1575)
    - [Five men sitting on a porch], 1
    - [Herbert Hoover and another man looking at a book], 2
    - [Photos of Lowell Thomas and other standing outside of a brick building], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and other standing outside a brick building], 4
    - [Three men standing together], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas and two men talking], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas dining with three other men], 7
    - Note [Envelope addressed to Lowell Thomas, Hemmersley Hill, Pawling, N.Y.], 8
  - Subject files: Horses, circa 1930s; 20 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas in the Arabian Desert, on and Arab thoroughbred], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas on a black horse], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas on a black horse], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas petting a horse], 4
  - Subject files: King Hussein of Jordan and Lowell Thomas, 1964; 21 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing at a podium, introducing King Hussein of Jordan], 1
  - Subject files: Marshal Joseph Joffre, undated; 22 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Marshal Joseph Joffre], 1
  - Subject files: Josephine Kaas, undated; 23 (Box 1575)
    - [A group of people looking at the pavement], 1
    - Note [Josephine Kaas], 2
    - [People standing on the edge of a pool], 3
    - [A four piece band playing in the grass], 4
    - [People out in the yard], 5
    - [Foxes in a cage], 6
    - [Foxes in a cage], 7
    - [A four-piece band playing in the grass], 8
    - [Children sitting around Josephine Kass (?)], 9
    - [Children looking at an indian headdress], 10
    - [The sky], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas in front of the camera], 12
  - Subject files: Hans von Kaltenborn, circa 1930s; 24 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a group of men], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group of men], 2
  - Subject files: King George of Greece, circa 1940s; 25 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with King George of Greece (?)], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with King George iof Greece (?)], 2
  - Subject files: Kirkman, Iowa, undated; 26 (Box 1575)
    - [Kirkman, Iowa], 1
  - Subject files: Thomas Lamont, Jr., undated; 27 (Box 1575)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting two two men preparing for a broadcast], 1
  - Subject files: Leather Trunk Series (Alaska), 1916; 28 (Box 1575)
    - [Ship in Alaska], 1
    - [Ship in Alaska], 2
    - [Alaskans in kayaks], 3
    - [People on a rocky beach], 4
    - [Two Alaskan children], 5
    - [An Alaskan town], 6
    - [Two men holding moose antlers in Alaska], 7
    - Note: [Joseph Hawkes letterhead. Thomas], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas on a boat in Alaska], 9
    - [Mountains and water in Alaska], 10
    - [Woman and girl in a garden in Alaska], 11
    - [Crowd of people boarding a ship in Alaska], 12
    - [View of the water from a boat in Alaska], 13
    - [Men standing outside the Regina Hotel in Alaska], 14
    - [Group of men standing outside the Regina Hotel in Alaska], 15
    - [Man standing on a boardwalk in Alaska], 16
    - Note: [L.T. (?) 60 cents], 17
  - Subject files: Leather Trunk Series - Eskimos, circa 1916; 29 (Box 1575)
    - [Rocky shore in Alaska], 1
    - [Eskimo woman with baby on her back in Alaska], 2
    - [Two men standing with furs in Alaska], 3
    - [Eskimos in front of a tent], 4
    - [Woman sitting on rocks in Alaska], 5
    - [River in Alaska], 6
    - [Eskimo family in Alaska], 7
    - Note [envelope from the Auditorium Hotel. Joseph Hawkes (?)], 8
  - Subject files: Leather Trunk Series - Grand Canyon, 1916; 30 (Box 1575)
    - Note [Lowell Thomas. 39 negatives of the Grand Canyon], 1
    - [Three men sitting on a fence at the Grand Canyon], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) in the Grand Canyon], 3
    - [Man (?) in at camp in the Grand Canyon], 4
    - [Man standing in a stream in the Grand Canyon], 5
    - [Man rubbing his foot in the Grand Canyon], 6
    - [Man walking through the Grand Canyon, 7
    - [Lake (?) in the Grand Canyon], 8
    - [The Grand Canyon], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) in a cable car in the Grand Canyon], 10
    - [Three men sitting on a fence in front of the Grand Canyon], 11
  - Subject files: Leather Trunk Series - President Woodrow Wilson, circa 1914 - 1916; 31 (Box 1575)
    - Note: President Wilson at Princeton [Woodrow Wilson], 1
    - [Bed], 2
    - [Group of people standing in front of a house], 3
    - [Group of people standing in front of a house], 4
    - [Woodrow Wilson walking with a group of people], 5
    - [Woodrow Wilson shaking hands with someone in front of a train], 6
  Box 1576
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Live broadcast on location, 1951; 1 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas Jr., and others doing a live broadcast on CBS], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas Jr., and other doing a live CBS broadcast (backwards!)], 2
    - Note [1 - 16 x 16 soft finish. Please darken the man in the light suit, standing, at right. His head is bent.], 3
  - Subject files: Maine Lumberjacks, circa 1930s; 2 (Box 1576)
    - [Photos of the Maine Lumberjacks band playing in the grass], 1
    - [The Maine lumberjacks dancing and playing instruments], 2
    - [Photos of the Maine Lumberjacks], 3
    - [The Maine Lumberjack band], 4
    - [The Maine Lumberjack band], 5
    - Note [N.Y. Strips. Square Dancing Country Club Maine Lumber Jacks], 6
  - Subject files: Marco Polo painting, circa 1960s - 1970s; 3 (Box 1576)
    - [Painting of Marco Polo], 1
    - [Painting of Marco Polo], 2
    - [Painting of Marco Polo], 3
    - [Painting of Marco Polo], 4
  - Subject files: Marist Honorary Degree, 1981; 4 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas being presented with the Marist Honorary Degree], 1
  - Subject files: George McManus, undated; 5 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas and George Marcus doing a broadcast on NBC], 1
  - Subject files: Montage photographs, circa 1960s - 1970s; 6 (Box 1576)
    - [Collage of photos], 1
    - [Collage of photos], 2
    - [Collage of photos], 3
    - [Collage of photos], 4
  - Subject files: Mount Rainier National Park, undated; 7 (Box 1576)
    - [Man riding on a horse at Mount Rainier National Park], 1
  - Subject files: Torakichi Nakamura (golf champion), undated; 8 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas with Torakichi Nakamura, golf champion], 1
  - Subject files: Jawaharlal Nehru, circa 1950s; 9 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with Jawaharlal Nehru], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and Jawaharlal Nehru], 2
  - Subject files: New Guinea, undated; 10 (Box 1576)
    - [Men in New Guinea], 1
  - Subject files: Nine Old Men softball team, circa 1930s; 11 (Box 1576)
    - [Man and woman sitting outside], 1
    - [Cartoon of the Nine Old Men softball team], 2
    - [Batter for the Nine Old Men softball team], 3
    - [Babe Ruth on a motorcycle], 4
    - [Babe Ruth on a motorcycle], 5
    - [The Nine Old m-Men softball team], 6
    - [Member of the Nine Old Men softball team], 7
    - [Pitcher for the Nine Old Men softball team], 8
    - [Members of the Nine Old Men softball team and a woman], 9
    - [Member of the Nine Old Men softball team getting into his uniform], 10
    - [Batter for the Nine Old Men softball team], 11
    - [Members of the Nine Old Men softball team], 12
    - [The Nine Old Men softball team], 13
    - [Member of the Nine Old Men softball team napping], 14
    - [The Nine Old Men softball team playing instruments], 15
    - [Member of the Nine Old Men softball team on base], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas and another member of the Nine Old Men softball team talking with members of the Statesmen softball team], 17
    - Note [Sir Hubert Wilkins Burns Them Over!], 18
  - Subject files: Olympics, 1968; 12 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas and two guys at the Olympics], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and man standing outside of an airplane], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with people at the Olympics], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a woman from the Olympics], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with a woman in front of a plane, 5
    - [Lowell Thomas with a man], 6
    - Note [Letter from the Desert News to Lowell Thomas, 7
    - Note [Envelope to Lowell Thomas from the Desert News], 8
  - Subject files: Olympics trophy, circa 1930s; 13 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas with the Olympics trophy], 1
  - Subject files: Bill Paley, undated; 14 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with Bill Paley], 1
  - Subject files: Passenger flight around the world (Pan American World Airways), 1947; 15 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking on the steps of a Pan American World Airways plane], 1
    - Note [Letter from Secretary to Lowell Thomas to Miss Clair], 2
    - Note [Note regarding Lowell Thomas's help in launching Pan American's first passenger flight around the world.], 3
    - Note [Letter from Althea Lister to Miss Mary Davis], 4
    - Note [Maurice T. Moore and Erwin D. Canham], 5
  - Subject files: Personalities, undated; 16 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with Eagan, McArthur, and Tunney (?)], 1
    - Note [L.T., Eagan, MacArthur, Tunney (?)], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man doing a NBC broadcast], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man doing a NBC broadcast], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas with Major Bowes, Ed Wynn, Jack Pearl, Paul Whiteman, David Warfield, and James A. Brady], 5
    - Note [VIII-3 Major Bowes, Ed Wynn, Jack Pearl, Paul Whiteman, David Warfield, James A. Brady], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and others at G.A. Richard's All-American 59th Birthday Party], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas looking at a program with another man], 8
  - Subject files: Personalities, undated; 17 (Box 1576)
    - Lowell Thomas standing with a group of men], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with two men], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas with a man], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas with two women in Japan], 4
    - Note [Lowell Thomas. Rockefeller. New York. Arthur "Bugs" Baer; some chap who was featured by Ripley in his Believe-It-Or-Not cartoon, a man who hadn't done anything, hadn't played baseball, hadn't been married, hadn't been to World's Fair etc,; Olsen of Hellzapoppin' and L.T.], 5
  - Subject files: Personalities, circa 1958 - 1981; 18 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a woman], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group of men], 2
    - [Three men talking], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking a man's hand], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with a man], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas being presented with an award, 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man doing a NBC broadcast], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas with two other men], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man broadcasting on NBC], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man doing a broadcast on NBC], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas with people at an event], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with three men at an event, 12
    - Note [L.T. + ?], 13
    - Note [Joe Brusis, LT + ?], 14
    - Note [Gov. Carr (c)], 15
    - Note [LT + Gen Mstrs (General Motors) exec? (executive)], 16
  - Subject files: Personalities, 1938 - 1980; 19 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a man], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with a man and woman at a banquet table], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with two women at an event ], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas with two men outside], 4
    - Note [LT, Gov. Carr, Danny (?) Sullivan (?)], 5
    - Note [Austrian who climbed Everest, LT astronauts], 6
    - Note [LT w/ Norman Rockwell], 7
  - Subject files: Personalities, 1923 - 1972; 20 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas Jr. (?) with a man at and event], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas, Lowell Thomas Jr., and a man], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas with three other men at an event], 3
  - Subject files: Personalities, 1938 - 1970; 21 (Box 1576)
    - [Lowell Thomas, Douglas MacArthur and another man at an event], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a man], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting outside with two men], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with two men], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and four men at a banquest table], 5
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas standing at a podium with two others], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. seated with man (Dr. Rusk?) standing], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. seated], 8
    - [Man standing [Colonel Stoopnagle?], woman seated], 9
    - [Man talking with Lowell Thomas, Jr.], 10
    - [Man holding frame at podium], 11
    - [Man speaking at podium], 12
    - [Photo of Lowell Thomas standing at a podium with two others], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas at podium, state seal of Nebraska], 14
    - Note: [Top half of The Fairborn Daily Herald December 18, 1978, story concerning anniversary of first flight], [PDF], 15
    - Note: [Bottom half of The Fairborn Daily Herald December 18, 1978, story concerning anniversary of first flight], [PDF], 16
    - Note: [Letter to Lowell Thomas from Maurice J. Murphy concerning photographs from National Capital Area Auto Show], 17
    - Note: [Letter to Lowell Thomas from Frank Hefter concerning Travel Hall of Fame], 18
    - Note: [reverse of letter from Frank Hefter] Neil Armstrong, (with glasses) George Allen, head of Boeing Aircraft Co, British Actor Robert Morley, 19
    - Note: [Letter to Lowell Thomas from Peter Grimm concerning luncheon where Mayor Wagner honored Herbert Hoover], 20
    - Note: [envelope from The Nutmegger], 21
    - Note: [Letter to Lowell Thomas from Maury Hanson of The Nutmegger magazine concerning photographs of Dr. Rusk], 22
    - Note: 18x10, 23